[
     {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 18?",
      "correctAnswer": "324",
      "options": [
        "322",
        "326",
        "329",
        "324"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 16?",
      "correctAnswer": "256",
      "options": [
        "261",
        "258",
        "254",
        "256"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 13?",
      "correctAnswer": "169",
      "options": [
        "171",
        "167",
        "169",
        "174"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "81",
      "options": [
        "81",
        "79",
        "83",
        "86"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 14?",
      "correctAnswer": "196",
      "options": [
        "201",
        "198",
        "194",
        "196"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "4",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "4",
        "2",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 7?",
      "correctAnswer": "49",
      "options": [
        "51",
        "54",
        "49",
        "47"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 14?",
      "correctAnswer": "196",
      "options": [
        "194",
        "198",
        "201",
        "196"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 20?",
      "correctAnswer": "400",
      "options": [
        "398",
        "400",
        "402",
        "405"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 11?",
      "correctAnswer": "121",
      "options": [
        "121",
        "126",
        "119",
        "123"
      ]
    }
]